How to wash the cow dung
Before this, creating the cow dung water washing effect has always been a very complicated process.
But with our new design, you can achieve this effect faster and more easily.
To turn on the water washing effect, please first select the fabric to apply the effect.
Then, under the type selection, switch the fabric from matte to cow dung.
Under the default setting, it is set to non-water washing.
But you can choose any water washing type and start to define yourself.
In this example, I will choose acid washing.
As you can see, the water washing effect has been successfully applied.
Now we can use some parameters to adjust the results.
The first is acid concentration.
This is the only setting that changes according to the water washing type.
It controls the strength or opacity of the water washing sticker.
You can also adjust the mixing mode.
Here I choose the stacking mode.
The absorption increases the blur or spread effect for the sticker.
It mimics the way the water wash is absorbed into the plant.
The cycle cycle can increase the brightness of the water wash.
The longer the water wash cycle is imitated, the brighter the surface effect is obtained.
Finally, the cow dung dung dung can strengthen the wrinkle texture of the clothes.
You can try this effect at will.
These values have reached the appearance you want.
Click on the water washing technique type, water washing pattern.
You can set the shrink, rotate, and balance of the water washing pattern.
You can enter specific values here to complete the adjustment.
As mentioned above, if you switch to a different water washing type,
you will see that the acid concentration has become another setting.
They have similar functions.
You can set other water washing settings to increase the authenticity of your work.
That's all for this video.
See you in the next video.